marylandpublicschools.org 2003-12-03

# MSDE Privacy Statement

**MSDE Privacy Statement**

Thank you for visiting the Maryland State Department of Education web site. We take data security and the privacy of your personal information very seriously. The Department is currently developing new data privacy and security policies, and will post those policies on this web site when adopted. The Department does not currently collect personal information from this web site. The Maryland School Performance Report web site ([msp.msde.state.md.us](http://www.msde.state.md.us/)) contains a separate [privacy statement](http://msp.msde.state.md.us/introduction/privacy.asp). The Department does comply with the Maryland law that mandates that State agencies shall not create personal records unless the need for the information is clearly established and that personal records shall be relevant to the purposes for which they are collected, be accurate and current, and not be obtained by fraudulent means. State officials who request personal data from citizens must notify the citizens regarding the purposes for which the information is collected; consequences to the citizen for refusing to provide the personal information; the citizen’s right to inspect and correct personal records; whether the information is generally available for public inspection; and whether the information is made available to other entities. Please refer to the eMaryland technology web site ([www.techmd.state.md.us](http://www.techmd.state.md.us/)) for additional information on information technology policies in Maryland. The Maryland State Department of Education is committed to providing you with web sites over which you may securely and confidently transact business with the State.

> **Maryland State Department of Education  
>  200 West Baltimore Street  
>  Baltimore, MD 21201  
>  (410) 767-0425   
>  (410) 333-6442 (TTY/TDD)  
>  (410) 333-2226 (Fax)**
